hkis.edu.hk 2015-12-19

# Hong Kong International School: Privacy Policy

### Links

HKIS is not responsible for the contents of external websites. HKIS provides links to other websites for relevance and interest and links do not substantiate endorsement. Please feel free to create a link to the HKIS website. If you would like us to link to your site, please contact us at [info@hkis.edu.hk](mailto:info@hkis.edu.hk) with the subject line **‘Link request’**.

### Use of Text and Images

If you would like to publish information contained on our website, please send your request to [info@hkis.edu.hk](mailto:info@hkis.edu.hk). Where text or images are posted on our site with the permission of the original copyright holder, a copyright statement appears at the bottom of the page.

### HKIS logo

The HKIS logo remains the property of HKIS at all times. If you would like to obtain information about using our logo, please contact us via [info@hkis.edu.hk](mailto:info@hkis.edu.hk) with the subject line “Logo request”.

### Accessibility

This website is designed to be accessible to visitors with disabilities. If you have suggestions on how to make the site more accessible we would welcome your comments via [info@hkis.edu.hk](mailto:info@hkis.edu.hk).

### Website data policy

We do not collect personally identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us. Providing such information is voluntary.

If you sign up for one of our email lists, we will only send you the kinds of information you have requested. We will not share your name or email address with any outside parties. We collect and store only the following information about you: the name of the domain from which you access the Internet (for example: .me, if you are connecting from a mobile me account, or hkis.edu.hk if you are connecting from HKIS's domain), the date and time you access our site, and the internet address of the website from which you linked to our site.

We use the information we collect to measure the number of visitors to the different sections of our site and to help us make our site more useful to visitors.

### Online Profile Updates and donations

If you complete the Profile Update form and share your personal information, this will be used only to provide you with more targeted content. We may use your contact information to send further information about our organization or to contact you when necessary. You may always opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the 'Change your contact information' section below.

### Sending us an email

You may decide to send us personally identifying information in an email containing a question or comment, or by filling out a web form that provides us with this information. We only use personally identifying information from your email to respond to your requests. We may forward your email to other employees who are better able to answer your questions. We may also use your email to contact you in the future about our programs that may be of interest.

### Children and privacy

For children who visit our site, special rules apply. We do not request personal information about children, such as first and last name or street address and city. When children send an email to us, their online contact information is not used to re-contact them and is not maintained in retrievable form

### Change your contact information

Our site provides users with the option to opt-out of receiving communications from us at any time. You may choose to receive only specific communications or none at all. You may also update your contact information previously provided to us. If you want to remove yourself from our database, please contact us via [info@hkis.edu.hk](mailto:info@hkis.edu.hk).

### Questions

If you have any questions about this website, you can contact us via [info@hkis.edu.hk](mailto:info@hkis.edu.hk).
